I can't understand what people are saying
어느 순간을 맞춰야 될지
한 발자국 떼면 한 발자국 커지는 shadow
잠에서 눈을 뜬 여긴 또 어디
어쩜 서울 또 New York or Paris
일어나니 휘청이는 몸
Look at my feet down
날 닮은 그림자
흔들리는 건 이놈인가
아니면 내 작은 발끝인가
두렵잖을 리 없잖아
다 괜찮을 리 없잖아
그래도 I know 서툴게 I flow
저 까만 바람과 함께 날아
Hey na na na
미치지 않으려면 미쳐려 해
나를 다 던져 이 두 쪽 세상에
Hey na na na
I can't hold me down cause you know I'm a fighter
제 발로 들어온 아름다운 감옥
Find me and I'm gonna live with ya
Jump hey oh
가져와 bring the pain oh yeah
올라타봐 bring the pain oh yeah
Rain be pourin' Sky keep fallin'
Every day oh na na
Jump hey oh
가져와 bring the pain oh yeah
Bring the pain
모두 내 피와 살이 되겠지
No fear 방법을 알겠으니
작은 것에 breathe
그건 어둠 속 내 산소와 빛
내가 나이게 하는 것들의 힘
넘어져도 다시 일어나 scream
언제나 우린 그랬으니
설령 내 무릎이 땅에 닿을지언정
파묻히지 않는 이상
그저 그런 해프닝쯤 될 거란 걸
We no matter what
We no matter who
네가 뭐라던 누가 뭐라던
I don't give a uh I don't give a uh
I don't give a uh yeah
Hey na na na
미치지 않으려면 미쳐야 해
나를 다 던져 이 두 쪽 세상에
Hey na na na
I can't hold me down 'cause you know I'm a fighter
제발로 들어온 아름다운 감옥
Find me and I'm gonna live with ya
Hey oh 가져와 bring the pain oh yeah
Hey oh 올라타 bring the pain oh yeah
Rain be pourin' Sky keep fallin'
Everyday oh na na na
Hey oh 가져와 bring the pain oh yeah
나의 고통이 있는 곳에
내가 숨쉬게 하소서
My everything
My blood and tears
Got no fear cause I'm singing oh
Oh I'm taking over
You should know yeah
I can't hold me down 'cause you know I'm a fighter
깜깜한 심연 속 기꺼이 잠겨
가져와 bring the pain oh yeah
Hey oh 올라타봐 bring the pain oh yeah
Rain be pourin' Sky keep fallin'
Everyday oh na na na
Hey oh find me and I'm gonna bleed with ya
Hey oh 가져와 bring the pain oh yeah
Hey oh 올라타 bring the pain oh yeah
All that I know is just goin' on and on and on and on
Hey oh 가져와 bring the pain oh yeah